Okay, we're going to start with the shower.
We're all done with the tub now.
Hopefully you have no questions left on the tub.
Its sparkly and clean.
There's no germs.
You know that its, its a clean place to wash.
So lets move on to the shower.
I'm going to give you an example of what I do with the squeegee.
Every time you take a shower, this is your best friend.
So lets get some water marks first to show you.
Lets get some water marks going right there.
Okay, now every time I take a shower.
You see these?
I don't know if you can see the water marks.
But every time you shower, if you use the squeegee to get rid of that water on your panels, there is so much less work to do when you have to come and clean your shower.
So from the inside, lets say I've just had a shower.
I pick up my squeegee, which is always on the floor in m tub.
And I just go from top to bottom, and it just helps so much with stopping that buildup of water marks or calcium from the water.
And just go like that.
Done.
And then obviously I did it to this side as well.
But it.
You would be amazed at how much easier it is to keep your glass clean if you just do that with no cleaning products at all.